Hey, now.
We called earlier, they said you were up...
and by the time we get here,
you're back asleep.
-Been there long?
-No.
20 minutes.
You know, we didn't want to
exactly disturb you.
I'm bored, is all.
Yeah, but still.
So, what you got for me?
-Spreads?
-Yeah.
Little Man. For sure.
That's good. Are you able to write?
Okay. Number two.
I can make Little Man,
because he's in the front...
trying to snatch the cash off the dashboard.
But the other one, he's outside in the dark.
-So....
-So, you know, it's okay.
Is there anyone here that you do recognize?
Sure. Wee-Bey.
All right.
Let me tell you where we're
coming from with the shooters.
We tracked their escape route,
and Landsman came up with their hoodies.
Now, DNA matched...
human hair from one of the hoodies
to Wee-Bey.
Freamon, he tracked
a call from the pay phone...
near the scene, to Stringer Bell's pager.
Now, the caller was
using Bey's beeper code.
Crime lab, they lift a print...
off a soda can near that phone,
and that matches Little Man.
You know, so, you know, I'm saying....
Okay, hear me out.
There's a downside here.
We don't have the guns...
no prints from the scene, no witnesses.
But worse, we're going to be dealing
with a Baltimore city jury...
and a good man is hard to find in this town.
Twelve of them together, especially.
An ID of both your shooters...
will play a whole lot easier come trial.
Yeah.
Sometimes things just got to play hard.
We got everyone on our list except C.C.O.
We hit his mama's house...
and she says that he went up
to Wabash for some court date.
You can get on the computer
and see if any of the Sheriff's deputies...
can snatch him up in some courtroom.
Yeah. No, we got Ronnie Moe.
I'm looking at him
go in the jail van right now.
All right.
-Fished our limit. Let's go home.
-"Sir."
-Huh?
-"Let's go home, sir."
You're looking at
a soon-to-be-made sergeant.
So what I'm saying is,
when we're around the troops...
you got to get used to
showing the proper respect.
So, "Let's go home, sir." All right?
What's the count?
So far we've picked up 1 2.
That leaves seven on the wing.
Anything worthwhile?
Some phone numbers that match,
scraps of nicknames, not much else.
We need something now.
They'll shut us down unless we come up
with something fresh to run with right now.
The wires are dead.
The bug in the club is useless.
They're moving out of there
even as we got up on them.
-To where?
-No clue.
But they're going to have to set up again.
Either Barksdale moves
to reset his distribution...
or he gives up the towers.
-If not Avon, then Stringer.
-And why not Avon?
With no priors, he's out
two hours after the bail review.
What we put on Barksdale
barely makes him break stride.
Okay, so we get a hint of
where they're setting back up.
We ask the State's Attorney for a new bug...
maybe even a wire if we get onto a phone.
Not while the deputy breathes air.
We'll be reassigned
before you finish typing up your affidavit.
How about the feds?
You think the Deputy's
going to let you take this mess federal?
Why does the Deputy need to know?
McNulty, you are a piece of work.
McNulty.
Yeah?
No shit.
No fucking shit.
It's Rhonda Pearlman.
She just got a call from an assistant
public defender in North Jersey...
who claims to represent
a man by the name of D'Angelo Barksdale.
Meet me in Homicide. Bring a tape recorder.
No drug lawyers? No Levy?
-Case got some legs on her, don't she?
-Don't she?
Quarter of a million dollars bail.
You believe that shit?
It hurts to even show that kind of money.
www.tvsubtitles.net